boxight.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy – Boxight

We highly value our customers and their privacy. Our privacy policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our customers. Your personal information is safe with us. All personal information collected on this site is kept strictly confidential and not sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned. Your personal information is used exclusively for the purpose of fulfilling your order and making your buying experience a success.

Boxight. (“Boxight”, ‘we’, ‘our’, ‘us’) respects the privacy rights of its online visitors (‘you’, ‘your’, ‘yours’) and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We provide this statement (the “Privacy Policy”) to help you to understand what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. This Privacy Policy guides how we collect, store and use the information that you provide us with.

By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and agree that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions, which govern, in general, your use of the website maintained and operated by Boxight (the “Site”). We will use your information only for the purposes set out below.

Although we are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust in all of our activities with you, this Privacy Policy does not govern our collection or use of data about you through channels other than the Site.

Please exit the Site immediately if you do not accept this Privacy Policy or are accessing the Site in a country or other territory where use of the Site is not permitted.

We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version.
